听力材料，听录音，根据个体要求
选择最佳答案。
每项内容读两遍。
第一节：听下面五段对话，选。
出与录音内容相一致的图片。
1. What is your favorite cartoon character?
Mickey Mouse. He's so funny that he makes me laugh a lot.
What is your favorite cartoon character?
2. I think I'm having trouble hearing things clearly.
You should go to a doctor.
Let's go this afternoon.
3. Carl, you missed the bus this morning, didn't you?
Yes, when I got to the the bus stop, it was 7.30.
The bus had left 15 minutes before.
Carl, you missed the bus this morning, didn't you?
Yes, when I got to the bus stop, it was 7.30.
The bus had left 15 minutes before.
4. What do you usually do to relax on weekends, Marc?
I like going swimming.
It makes me feel cool and comfortable.
5. Dad, I'm so tired.
I want to relax in the coffee shop.
Come on, Amy.
Your mother is waiting for us in the flower shop.
Dad, I'm so tired.
I want to relax in the coffee shop.
Come on, Amy.
Your mother is waiting for us in the flower shop.
2. B, and We enjoyed ourselves during the trip.
第二节。
听下面五段对话。
或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听每段对话或独白前，
你家有时间阅读。
各个小题，每小题五秒钟，
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
听第六段材料，回答第六至八题。
Did you travel with your parents?
Not really. Just my mother and I went there.
My father was busy with his work.
How did you prepare for the trip?
First, I made a travel plan and then I bought the air tickets online.
When we arrived in London, I took my mom to different places of interest.
Wow! How great you are!
Daniel, how was your trip to London?
It was relaxing and interesting.
We enjoyed ourselves during the trip.
Did you travel with your parents?
Not really. Just my mother and I went there.
My father was busy with his work.
How did you prepare for the trip?
First, I made a travel plan and then I bought the air tickets online.
When we arrived in London, I took my mom to different places of interest.
Wow! How great you are!
听第七段才。
材料，回答第九至十一题
Answer to eleventh questions.
Answer Answer Oh, it's already 10.30.
We've spent one and a half hours watching TV.
It's time for us to take a break from the television.
But I'm waiting for a new TV program.
It's a talk show.
You know I like talk shows very much.
too much TV is bad for our eyes.
Let's do some sports outside.
Maybe I should do my homework at home.
No. You should go out and take in some fresh air.
Let's play tennis.
It's so boring.
Are you interested in volleyball?
I can teach you how to play it.
Okay. Let's go.
Oh, it's already 10.30.
We've spent one and a half hours watching TV.
It's time for us to take a break from the television.
But I'm waiting for a new TV program.
It's a talk show.
You know I like talk shows very much.
Watching too much TV is bad for our eyes.
Let's do some sports outside.
Maybe I should do my homework at home.
No. You should go out and take in some fresh air.
Let's play tennis.
It's so boring.
Are you interested in volleyball?
I can teach you how to play it.
Okay. Let's go.
Listen Peter, I am a reporter from the school radio station.
听第八段材料，回答第十二至十四题。
You did very well in the English speech.
Thank you. Can I ask you some questions?
Of course you can.
How do you learn English so well?
I often read good articles in English magazines and memorize them.
Do you have a pen pal?
Yes. He is a tall and thin boy from Sydney.
He has helped me a lot.
How often do you write to each other?
About once a week.
Do you go to the English corner to practice your spoken English?
Yes. There are many foreigners and I have made many friends there.
Last question. What do you often talk about in the English corner?
We often talk about cultures in different countries.
Peter, I am a reporter from the school radio station.
You did very well in the English speech.
Thank you. Can I ask you some questions?
Of course you can.
How do you learn English so well?
I often read good articles in English magazines and memorize them.
Do you have a pen pal?
Yes. He is a tall and thin boy from Sydney.
He has helped me a lot.
How often do you write to each other?
About once a week.
Do you go to the English corner to practice your spoken English?
Yes. There are many foreigners and I have made many friends there.
Last question. What do you often talk about in the English corner?
We often talk about cultures in different countries.
听第九段材料，回答第十五至十七题。
Hi, Sarah. Did you get the theater tickets?
There were no tickets for Friday or Saturday, so we're going on Thursday instead.
That's okay. Where are we sitting?
They only had seats in the middle or at the back.
There weren't any left at the front.
Well, I didn't get seat at the back because I sat there last time and I couldn't
hear anything. Are they expensive?
Because we're students, they're only 7 pounds each.
I think I'll take 10 pounds so I can buy an ice cream.
Great. I can't wait.
Hi, Sarah. Did you get the theater tickets?
There were no tickets for Friday or Saturday, so we're going on Thursday instead.
That's okay. Where are we sitting?
They only had seats in the middle or at the back.
There weren't any left at the front.
Well, I didn't get seat at the back because I sat there last time and I couldn't
hear anything. Are they expensive?
Because we're students, they're only 7 pounds each.
I think I'll take 10 pounds so I can buy an ice cream.
Great. I can't wait.
听第十段材料，回答第十八至二十题。
It was the second Sunday of May, Mother's Day.
In the morning, when Tom's mother got up, she found there were some beautiful
flowers near her bed.
She liked them very much.
After she washed her face and went into the kitchen, the delicious breakfast was
ready on the table.
She was surprised to see her husband, Mr.
Smith, and her son, Tom Smith, were both at the table waiting for her.
Happy Mother's Day, Mom, said Tom.
She remembered that it was Mother's Day.
Mr. told her that Tom swept the and cooked two eggs for her, and Mr.
Smith washed all the dirty clothes.
Thanks a lot.
You're both my love, said Mrs.
happily. And in the evening, when she came back home from work by bus, she found a
message on the table that asked her to have dinner in a restaurant with the name of
Mother. How happy she was!
It was the second Sunday of May, Mother's Day.
In the morning, when Tom's mother got up, she found there were some beautiful
flowers near her bed.
She liked them very much.
After she washed her face and went into the kitchen, the delicious breakfast was
ready on the table.
She was surprised to see her husband, Mr.
Smith, and her son, Tom Smith, were both at the table waiting for her.
Happy Mother's Day, Mom, said Tom.
She remembered that it was Mother's Day.
Mr. told her that Tom swept the floor and cooked two eggs for her, and Mr.
Smith washed all the dirty clothes.
Thanks a lot.
You're both my love, said Mrs.
happily. And in the evening, when she came back home from work by bus, she found a
message on the table that asked her to have dinner in a restaurant with the name of
Mother. How happy she was!
Happy